（リムル）
暴風竜ヴェルドラを
封印する無限牢獄(ろうごく)
The Storm Dragon Veldora was
sealed by Unlimited Imprisonment.
Unlimited Imprisonment
To break that seal, Rimuru ate Veldora.
その封印を打ち破るため
リムルはヴェルドラを捕食した
ヴェルドラは封印の中から
They both began the process
of analyzing the seal,
Veldora from the inside and
Rimuru from the outside,
リムルは封印の外から
解析を続ける
with the goal of setting
Veldora free someday.
いつか
ヴェルドラを解放するために
いくつものスキルを得つつ
洞窟を出たリムルは
After gaining several new
skills and leaving the cave,
Rimuru met the Goblins,
ゴブリンたちと遭遇
and he ended up vowing to protect
them from an attack by Direwolves.
牙狼族(がろうぞく)の襲撃から
ゴブリンたちを守ることに
なってしまった
That Time I Got Reincarnated as a Slime
Episode 3: Battle at the Goblin Village
Looks like I shouldn't expect to
find many who can fight Direwolves.
牙狼族と戦うのは
あんまり期待できそうにないな
貧弱そうだし… ボロボロ
They all look too scrawny and beat-up.
Talk about pressure...
プレッシャーだなあ
Everyone, do you understand our situation?
（リムル）
みんな 状況は分かっているか？
Yes!
（リーダー）はい！
We are prepared for a life-or-death battle!
生きるか死ぬかの戦いになると
覚悟はできております！
No need to get all worked up. Just relax.
（リムル）
気負うことはない　気楽にな
Think only about doing the best you can.
最善を尽くす
そのことだけを考えろ！
（ゴブリンたち）わあ〜！
I didn't mean to sound that cool...
（リムル）
かっこいいこと言っちゃった…
まずは 負傷者の所へ案内してくれ
But first, take me to where the wounded are.
We did all we could for them, but...
（村長）
できるだけの手当てはしましたが…
（ゴブリンＡ）ハア…
That's deeper than I'd imagined.
（リムル）
思った以上に深いな…
爪や牙で引き裂かれたのか
Did their claws and fangs
do that much damage?
Well, might as well try it...
まあ やってみるか
（村長）リッ リムル様 何を…
Wh-What are you doing?!
Huh? I'm...
あれ？　俺…
Y-Your wounds...
きっ 傷が…
治っている！
They're healed!
（リムル）
わお！　やってみるもんだな
I guess it never hurts to try!
I never thought eating him and throwing
all those potions in my body at him
捕食し 体内にためてある回復薬を
ぶっかけただけで
would be so effective!
こんなに効果があるとは
These healing potions really work!
すげえ効能だな 回復薬！
（リムル）
ほい 次　ほい 次！
Next! And next!
Since I ate all those hipokute
herbs, I've got plenty to spare!
ヒポクテ草 食いまくって
ストックは たっぷりある
I'll heal 'em all!
全員 治してやる！
（ゴブリンたち）ぶへ！　べへ！
うわ！　だあ！　ほえ！
Y-You are magnificent, Great Rimuru!
（村長）さ… さすがはリムル様
（村長）は… ははあ！
（ゴブリンたち）ははあ！
That's the last of the wounded.
（リムル）
ケガ人は これで全部だな
では…
Now, then...
We'll build a fence.
（リムル）
柵を作る！
村の防備を固めるぞ
Fortify the village's defenses!
（ゴブリンたち）うん！
（村長）はい
Right.
Great Forest of Jura
It's a fine night.
（ボス）いい夜だ
Veldora's protection has
vanished from this forest.
この森から
ヴェルドラの加護は失われた
We have nothing to fear any longer.
恐るるものは もうない
Tonight, we will destroy the Goblin Village
今夜 あのゴブリンの村を滅ぼし
and create a foothold here
in the Great Forest of Jura!
このジュラの森への足がかりを
作ろうぞ！
We will rule this forest!
（ボス）
我らは
この森の支配者となるのだ！
Our claws can tear apart any monster,
（ボス）
我らの爪は
いかなる魔物も引き裂き
and our fangs can chew any monster to pieces!
牙は いかなる魔物をも食い破る！
Hah!
（ボス）
フン！
あのような貧弱な柵 何の役に立つ
What good will such a flimsy fence do?
Father...
（息子）親父(おやじ)殿…
A slime?
（ボス）スライム？
Turn back now, and we won't take any action.
（リムル）
このまま引き返すなら何もしない
Leave this place at once!
さっさと立ち去るがいい！
（ボス）こざかしい！
Insolence! No mere slime can
order around us Direwolves!
スライムごときが
我ら牙狼に命令するな
Trample down that fence!
あの柵を なぎ倒せ！
Spill the blood of those lowly Goblins!
ゴブリンどもを血祭りにあげろ！
フンッ
（牙狼）グガア！
（ボス）なっ…
（牙狼たち）ギャン！
グガア！
Threads?
糸！
That's my skill, Steel Thread.
（リムル）
スキル〝鋼糸(こうし)〞だ
— Steel Thread —
（ボス）貴様の仕業か
This is your doing?
That's right!
（リムル）そうだ！
A puny monster like you dares do this?!
（ボス）矮小(わいしょう)なる魔物の分際(ぶんざい)で…
I will squash you!
ひねり潰してやる！
Father!
（息子）親父殿！
リムル様！
Great Rimuru!
That's Sticky Thread.
— Sticky Thread —
（リムル）〝粘糸(ねんし)〞さ
This won't hold me!
（ボス）これしき！　ぐっ…
Skill: Water Blade!
（リムル）スキル…
“水刃(すいじん)”！
Hear me, Direwolves!
（リムル）聞け！　牙狼族よ
Your boss is dead!
お前たちのボスは死んだ！
I'll give you the choice: submit or die!
選択をさせてやる
服従か 死か！
Yikes...
（リムル）
ヤバいなあ
What if they go the "We'd rather die than
submit" route and attack all at once?
服従するなら死を… 的なノリで
一斉に向かってきたら どうしよう
I wish they'd just turn tail and run...
逃げてってくんないかな…
Oh! Predator!
（リムル）捕食！
（大賢者(だいけんじゃ)）
解析が終了しました
Analysis complete.
Acquired ability to mimic Direwolf.
Acquired ability to mimic Direwolf
Direwolf species skills Supreme Sense of Smell,
Thought Communication, and Menace acquired.
牙狼 固有スキル“超嗅覚”
Thought
Communication
Supreme Sense
of Smell
Direwolf Species Skills
Menace
“思念伝達”“威圧”を
獲得しました
Right!
（リムル）よし！
— Mimic —
（リムル）クックック… 聞け！
Hear me! I will let you go just this once.
今回だけは見逃してやろう
If you refuse to yield to me,
I will allow you to leave this place!
我に従えぬと言うならば
この場より立ち去ることを許そう！
— Menace —
（ゴブリンたち）わあ〜！
（リムル）
ほらほら 早く逃げてくれ
Come on, run away already!
（リムル）アオ〜ン！
It's not working? They still want to fight?
（リムル）
ダメか… まだ戦うつもりか？
（リムル）アオ〜ン！
（息子）クウン…
（牙狼たち）
我ら一同 あなた様に従います！
Our pack yields to you.
（リムル）
え？
逃げてくれてよかったのにな…
Huh?
They could have just run away...
U-Um...
（リーダー）あっ あの…
D-Did we win?
（村長）か… 勝ったのですか？
Yeah, looks that way.
（リムル）あ〜 そうみたいだな
It's good that there's no
need for fighting anymore.
争う必要がなくなったのは
いいことだ
Yep, yep. Nothing beats peace.
うんうん 平和がいちばん！
（ゴブリンたち）やった〜！
And so the battle at the Goblin
Village ended remarkably easily.
（リムル）
こうして ゴブリン村の戦いは
実にあっさり終結したのだった
But...
しかし…
What now?
（リムル）
どうすんだ？
ゴブリンだけじゃなくて
Who's gonna look after not only the
Goblins, but all these pups, too?
こんなたくさんの犬どもの面倒
誰が見るんだよ
I guess their numbers are
about the same. Then...
どっちも同じぐらいか
じゃあ…
Okay, listen up!
（リムル）
はい 聞いてくださ〜い！
え〜っと これから 君たちには
So, I'm going to have you all
pair up and live together!
ペアになって 一緒に
過ごしてもらうことになりま〜す！
Pair... up?
Do you understand?
（リムル）意味は分かるか？
（村長）
リムル様
“ぺあ”とは 一体 何ですかな？
Great Rimuru, what does "pair" mean, exactly?
It means to form groups of two.
（リムル）２人１組になってくれ
Groups...
（ゴブリン）２人…
（牙狼）１組？
...of two?
（リムル）
よし！　昨日の敵は今日の友！
Good!
Yesterday's enemy is today's friend!
You're all to work together and get
along as friends from now on! Got it?
これからは互いに力を合わせて
仲良くするんだぞ
いいな？
Yes, sir!
（ゴブリンたち）はい！
（牙狼たち）はっ！
Help each other out, and make it work.
（リムル）
互いに互いを助けて
うまくやるように
（リムル）
ハア… とりあえずは これでよし
That settles things for now...
So, um...
（リムル）それで え〜っと…
What's going to be important now
is food, shelter, and clothing.
これから大切なのは
衣 食 住です
食べ物を探し 家を作ったり
We should form teams to hunt
for food, build houses,
and strengthen the village defenses.
村の守りを固めたりするための
チームを作ろうと思う
まずは…
We'll start with...
What was his name again?
（リムル）
そういえば 名前 何だっけ…
っていうか 名前 あったっけ？
Wait, do they even have names?
Hey, what are all of your names, anyway?
（リムル）
お前たち そういえば 名前は？
We monsters do not normally have names.
普通 魔物は名前を持ちません
名前がなくとも
意思の疎通はできますからな
Even without names, we can still
communicate our thoughts to one another.
Oh, really?
（リムル）そうなのか
But it's more convenient to have names,
でも あったほうが便利だから
so I'd like to name you all. Is that okay?
お前たちに名前を付けようと思うが
いいか？
N-Name us?
（村長）
なっ 名前…
よっ よろしいのですか？
A-Are you certain?
S-Sure.
（村長）だあ〜！
Why are they so excited over something
as simple as getting a name?
（リムル）
なんで… 名前を付けるぐらいで
そんなに興奮してるんだ？
（村長）名前 名前…
（リムル）じゃあ 村長から
Okay, we'll start with you.
え〜っと そうだな…
Hmm, let's see...
What did you call the son
you had who died in battle?
亡くなった戦士の息子は
何ていう名だったんだ？
リグルです
Rigur.
Rigur, huh?
（リムル）リグルか…
Then you'll be Rigurd.
なら… リグルドだ
Rigurd!
リグルド！
はあ… ありがとうございます！
リグルド 感激です
Thank you so much! Rigurd! I am so moved!
（村長の泣き声）
（リムル）そ… そうか
R-Really?
I just picked it because
it had the same sound...
（リムル）
語呂がよかっただけなんだが…
You'll inherit your brother's name: Rigur.
（リムル）
お前は兄の名を継げ　リグルだ
は… はい！
Yes, sir!
I'm so grateful that my son has been
allowed to inherit Rigur's name!
息子に
リグルの名を継がしていただき
感謝感激です
Thank you so much!
（２人）ありがとうございます！
Where the heck are these
reactions coming from?
（リムル）
何なんだ？
このリアクションは…
You're Gobta.
（リムル）お前は ゴブタ
Y-Yes, sir! Thank you, sir!
（ゴブタ）
は… はい！
ありがとうございます！
You're Gobchi.
（リムル）お前はゴブチ
Gobtsu.
（リムル）ゴブツ
ゴブテ
Gobte.
お前はゴブゾウな
And you're Gobzo.
These names are getting
more and more careless...
（リムル）
だんだん適当になっていく…
喜んでくれてるのに 悪いな
I feel bad seeing them so happy.
Um... We truly do appreciate
you giving us all names, but...
（リグルド）
あの… 名前を付けていただくのは
大変ありがたいのですが
（リグルド）
リムル様の魔力が強大なのは
存じておりますが
We are aware that your
magical power is immense,
but are you sure it's all right
to give all of us names at once?
そのように
一度に名を与えられるなど
大丈夫なのですか？
（リムル）
ん？　まあ 問題ないだろ
Well, I don't see any problem.
Well, if you are certain...
（リグルド）それならば まあ…
Who's next?
（リムル）次は？
You'll be... Haruna!
お前は… ハルナ
（ハルナ）はい！
Okay!
（リムル）
ゴブリンたちは
全員 付け終わったな
That takes care of all the Goblins.
Next is...
次は…
He's the son of the Direwolf boss, isn't he?
牙狼族のボスの息子だよな…
俺のこと 恨んだりしてないのか？
I wonder if he holds a grudge against me...
Actually...
ていうか…
They don't seem to be
holding any grudges at all.
恨んでは… いないようだな
Hmm...
ふむ　オオカミ 牙…
Wolf, fangs...
Wind... Storm...
風 暴風…
そうか
俺のファミリーネームをやるか
I know. I'll give him my family name.
テンペスト テンペストの牙
嵐の牙 らんが…
Tempest...
Tempest Fang...
Storm Fang...
Ranga...
Oh! Ranga! I like that!
おっ “ランガ”！　いいね
All right! Your name is Ranga!
（リムル）
よし！　お前はランガ
— (Storm)   (Fang) —
Ranga...
（ランガ）ランガ…
I think he likes it.
（リムル）
喜んでる 喜んでる
Wh-What's going on? My body...
（リムル）
なっ 何だ？　体が…
（ランガ）リムル様！
Great Rimuru?!
（リムル）
目の前が 暗く…
Everything... is getting... dark...
（ゴブリンたち）
リムル様！
お気を確かに！
Great Rimuru!
Please stay strong!
Warning.
Warning
（大賢者）
告(こく)…
Magicule reserves below minimum limit
Internal magicule reserves have
fallen below the minimum limit.
体内の魔素(まそ)残量が
一定値を割り込みました
Entering sleep mode.
スリープモードへと移行します
Estimated time to full recovery: three days.
完全回復の予想時刻は ３日後です
I used up too many magicules?
（リムル）
魔素の使い過ぎ？　なんで…
How...?
I couldn't move, speak,
or sense my surroundings,
（リムル）
動けず しゃべれず
周囲を感じることはできないが
意識はあった
but I was conscious.
ああ… あんなに たくさん
一度に名前を付けていただいたから
It must have been because he
named so many of us at once...
Apparently, giving names to
monsters uses up magicules.
（リムル）
どうやら 魔物に名前を付けると
魔素を消費するということのようだ
I guess that's why Rigurd was so worried.
だから リグルドは
心配していたのだろう
Is that common knowledge among monsters?
魔物の常識か？
って はっきり言えよ！
You should've said so!
Then, three days later...
（リムル）
そして ３日後…
Full recovery!
（リムル）完　全　復　活！
（ハルナ）
まあ リムル様
おはようございます！
Oh, Great Rimuru!
Good morning!
Y-Yeah...
（リムル）おっ おう…
You seem to be all better.
すっかり よろしいようですね
Who's this?
（リムル）
誰？
I'll go get Elder Rigurd.
（ハルナ）
今 リグルド村長を
呼んでまいりますね
Uh, okay.
（リムル）あっ はい
Did this village have a girl that cute in it?
あんな美人 村にいたっけ？
Great Rimuru! Have you awakened?!
（リグルド）
リムル様！
お目覚めになられましたか！
Oh, Rigurd!
（リムル）おお リグルド
さっきの女性… は…
That woman who... was... just...
Who are you?!
誰だよ！
I am Rigurd.
（リグルド）リグルドです
What happened in the last three days?!
（リムル）３日の間に 一体 何が？
It's because you gave us names!
名前を頂いたからです！
Just from that?!
（リムル）それだけで？
Becoming a monster with a name
（リグルド）
名持ちの魔物になるということ
raises one's rank as a monster
and causes one to evolve!
それは 魔物としての格を上げ
進化をもたらすのです
（リグルド）ニッ！
（リムル）なっ なるほど…
I-I see...
So that's why you were all so
happy just to be getting names.
（リムル）
それで 名前を付けるってだけで
あんなに大喜びしてたのか
俺の魔素が
ごっそり吸い取られるわけだ
No wonder that sucked my magicules dry...
Master, allow me to express my
utmost joy at your recovery!
ご回復 心よりお喜び申し上げます
That horn... The star on your forehead...
（リムル）
その角 額の星… ランガだよね？
You're Ranga, right?
Yes!
（ランガ）はい！
Great Rimuru!
（ゴブリンたち）リムル様〜！
リムル様！　リムル様〜！
There's Rigurd...
（リムル）
リグルドに…
リグル
And Rigur...
And Gobta...
ゴブタ…
Well, you didn't change much.
お前は あんまり変わってないな
（一同）リムル様！　リムル様！
Great Rimuru! Great Rimuru!
（リムル）
ていうか 進化というより
もう こりゃ別の魔物だな
It's not so much like they evolved.
They're like totally different monsters.
The male Goblins have evolved to Hobgoblins,
（大賢者）
雄のゴブリンは“ホブゴブリン”に
and the females to Goblinas.
雌のゴブリンは
“ゴブリナ”に進化しています
Ranga, if I recall, you were
the only Direwolf I named...
（リムル）ランガ
俺は お前の名前しか
付けてないはずだが…
so why did all of the Direwolves evolve?
なんで
牙狼たち全員が進化してるんだ？
Master, all of us Direwolves are as one.
（ランガ）我が主よ！
我ら牙狼族は
“全にして個”なのです
Our brethren are all connected.
同胞は皆 つながっております
Therefore, my name has
become our clan's name.
故に
我が名は種族名となったのです！
（リムル）
ふむ… 共通の名として
種族全体が進化したのか
Huh... So your entire clan
evolved through a shared name?
We are no longer the Direwolves.
（ランガ）
もはや 我らは
牙狼族ではありません
We are the Tempest Wolves!
〝テンペストウルフ〞
です
Tempest Wolves...
（リムル）テンペストウルフ…
Well, good for you!
まっ よかったな！
Master!
（ランガ）我が主〜！
Can't you show a little consideration?!
（リムル）
ちょっとは迷惑を考えろ！
（ランガ）も… 申し訳ありません
I-I'm so sorry!
You can change your own size?! That's handy!
（リムル）
体の大きさまで変えられるのか
便利だな
Well, the evolving isn't so bad.
（リムル）
まあ 進化はいいとして
The problem is what to
do about food, shelter,
問題は
ゴブリンと狼たちが暮らすために
and clothing to sustain both
the Goblins and the Wolves...
衣食住をどうするかだ…
Master!
（ランガ）我が主〜！
（リムル）フウ…
Right, it took five minutes
for all of you to quiet down.
はい 今 みんなが静かになるまで
５分かかりました！
They didn't get my best joke?!
（リムル）
俺の持ちネタが通じないだと？
Great Rimuru, what did you mean by that?
（リグルド）
リムル様 何ですか 今のは？
（リムル）フッ… きっ 気にするな
F-Forget about it.
見てのとおり
俺たちは大所帯になった
As you can see, we're a huge family now.
そこで
トラブルを避けるため
So to avoid problems, I think
we should set some rules.
ルールを決めようと思う
Rules?
（一同）ルール？
（リムル）
ルールは３つ
最低 この３つは守ってほしい
There are three rules.
I'd like you to uphold
them, at the very least.
First, no attacking humans.
１つ 人間を襲わない
２つ 仲間内で争わない
Second, no fighting amongst yourselves.
３つ 他種族を見下さない
Third, no belittling other races.
以上！
That's it.
（リグル）はい！
Sir!
Yes, Rigur-kun!
（リムル）
はい リグル君
なぜ 人間を
襲ってはならないのでしょうか？
Why aren't we allowed to attack humans?
H-Hey! Rigur!
（リグルド）こ… こら リグル！
It's all right.
（リムル）いいから いいから
The reason is simple.
簡単な理由だ
It's because I like humans. That's it!
俺が人間を好きだから　以上！
なるほど！　理解しました
I see! Now I understand!
（リムル）
えっ 理解… しちゃった？
ホント？
Huh? You... understand?
Really?
Um, so, listen... Humans live in groups.
（リムル）
え〜っとな
人間は集団で生活してる
If you mess with them,
they could retaliate in a big way.
手を出すと
大きな反動が来る場合もある
本気で向かってこられると
太刀打ちできないだろう
And if they came after us in earnest,
I doubt we could handle them.
Besides, getting along benefits
us in lots of ways, anyway.
それに 仲良くするほうが
いろいろと得だしな
Any other questions?
（リムル）ほかに何かあるか？
（ゴブタ）はい！
（リムル）ゴブタ君
Me!
Gobta-kun!
“他種族を見下さない”
というのは？
What did you mean by
"no belittling other races"?
Well, you've all gotten
stronger by evolving, right?
（リムル）
お前たちは
進化して強くなっただろ？
It means you shouldn't let that get to
your head and push weaker races around.
調子に乗って 弱い種族に
偉そうにするなよって意味だ
偉くなったと勘違いするな
Don't make the mistake of thinking
you're better than them.
You don't want them getting stronger
themselves and retaliating someday, do you?
いつか相手が強くなって
仕返しされても つまらないだろ？
Got it, sir!
（ゴブタ）分かりましたっす！
That's about it. Do your
best to follow those rules.
（リムル）
そんなところだ
なるべく守るようにしてくれ
Yes, sir!
（一同）はい！
Also...
（リムル）それとだ…
村長リグルド
Elder Rigurd, I declare you the Goblin Lord.
君を“ゴブリン･ロード”に
任命する
ゴブリンの長(おさ)だ！
The lord of the Goblins!
Lord?!
（リグルド）
おさ！
Lead your village well.
（リムル）村をうまく治めるように
Yes, sir!
（リグルド）
ははっ！　このリグルド
I, Rigurd, accept this
responsibility on pain of death!
この身命を賭して その任
引き受けさせていただきます！
Good. I'm counting on you.
（リムル）うむ 任せた
Frankly, I was just dumping the job on
him. I didn't expect him to be so moved.
（リムル）
ぶっちゃけ 丸投げなのに
こんなに感動されてしまった
I then gave jobs to all the Goblins.
（リムル）
俺はゴブリンたちに役割を与えた
村の周囲を警戒するチームに…
I assigned a team to keep watch
on the surrounding area...
and a team to gather food.
食料調達チーム
It doesn't look like there'll
be any problems with these two.
この２つは特に問題なさそうである
The problem is...
問題は…
The team that builds houses, and
the team that makes clothes.
家を作るチームと衣服を作るチーム
The "shelter and clothing" part
of "food, shelter, and clothing."
衣食住の“衣”と“住”の部分だ
I wouldn't call that a house.
（リムル）家とは呼べないな
I can't do any more than
basic handyman stuff,
（リムル）
俺も日曜大工レベルしかできないが
but I worked in general contracting,
so I know good from bad.
ゼネコン勤務だったので
よしあしは分かる
And this...
これは…
You don't need to be a general
contractor to figure it out.
ゼネコン勤務でなくても分かるか…
This is most embarrassing.
お恥ずかしい話です
Forgive us.
すみません
And as for your clothes...
（リムル）それと 衣服だが…
（リムル）
ちょ… ちょっと露出し過ぎかな
I-I think they're a little too revealing!
That's not necessarily a bad thing, but...
それが悪いというわけでもないが…
There is no one here with
the skill to make them.
（リグル）
技術を持った者がいないのです
Huh?
つ… 作れないなら
調達できないのか？
I-If you can't make them,
couldn't you get some from somewhere?
今まで何度か 取り引きを
したことのある者たちがおります
There are some with whom we have
attempted to trade a few times.
Aside from clothing,
they are also quite skilled,
衣服の調達もですが
器用な者たちなので
家の作り方も存じておるやも
so they may know how to build houses, too.
Hmm...
（リムル）ふむ…
Well, we're getting nowhere this way,
これじゃあ どうにもならないから
ちょっと会いに行ってみるか
so maybe we should go see them.
Who, and where, are they?
どこの誰だ？
They are the Dwarves,
and they live in Dwargon.
ドワルゴンに住むドワーフ族です
Dwarves!
（リムル）
ドワーフ！　鍛冶の達人！
あの有名な？
You mean the famous
masters of metalworking?!
Now I have no choice but to go!
（リムル）
こりゃあ 行くしかない！
そのドワルゴンとやらに行ってみる
I'll try going to Dwargon.
Rigurd, can you look after
the village while I'm away?
リグルド
留守の間は任せていいか？
Yes, sir!
Leave everything to me!
お任せあれ〜
All right, I'll see you later!
（リムル）
じゃあ いってきま〜す！
Goodbye!
（一同）いってらっしゃ〜い！
（リグルド）お気をつけて！
Safe travels!
Come back soon!
（ハルナ）お早いお帰りを！
And so I left the village
to go and meet the Dwarves.
（リムル）
こうして俺は
ドワーフに会うため 村を出発した
なんでも
ドワーフの住むドワルゴンとやらは
I'm told this Dwargon place
is a pretty big city,
結構 大きな町で 王様もいるらしい
and it even has a king.
I'm a little... no, I'm really excited!
ちょっと…
いや だいぶ楽しみである
Next time, "In the Kingdom of the Dwarves."
（大賢者）
次回「ドワーフの王国にて」
In the Kingdom of the Dwarves